MUHAMMAD ASHRAF HAFIFIE BIN SHAARI

I'm an Electrical Engineering student and will be graduating in October 2017. I am extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills in any field that I get into. I like challenges because it can help me improve my working quality and experience.

Contact Info

017 478 1553

ashrafhafifie93@gmail.com

512, Permatang Tinggi Bakar

Bata, 13200 Kepala Batas,

Penang

Education

UNIVERSITI TUN HUSSEIN ONN 2014-2017 MALAYSIA

> BACHELOR DEGREE IN ELECTRICAL **ENGINEERING with HONOURS**

GPA 2.8

2011-2012

UNIVERSITI TUN HUSSEIN ONN MALAYSIA

DIPLOMA IN ELECTRICAL **ENGINEERING GPA 3.73**

Achievement & Participation

2014-2015

Students Representative Council UTHM (Committee)

JUNE & SEPTEMBER 2015

Minggu Haluan Siswa UTHM (Orientation Week) (Director)

Awards

 Deputy Vice Chancellor Award (Leadership) in Majlis Anugerah Pelajar UTHM 2016

Reference

Dr. Muhammad Saufi bin Kamarudin Academic Advisor Universiti Tun Hussein Onn Malaysia 012-735 3138

Experience

FEBRUARY 2017 -PRESENT

TUAH USAHA SDN. BHD. Assist. M&E Coordinator

• Incharged in coordinating the sub contractors in the field of electrical and mechanical.

JUNE 2016 -SEPTEMBER 2016 INFINITY PROSPECT (M) SDN. BHD.

Industrial Trainee

- Involved in the technical team
- Took part in setting up the lighting and sound system during event.

JUNE 2013 -SEPTEMBER 2013 BERJAYA AUTOMATION SDN. BHD.

Industrial Trainee

- Involved in one of the engineers
- Took part in site visit to supervise the workers

Personal Skills

MS Word •••••• MS Excel •••••• **MS** Powerpoint •••••• **AutoCAD**

••••••

Skills

Photoshop

Creativity •••••• Teamwork Organization Flexibility

Communication Leadership ••••••